<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>tellico.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>Tellico</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Tellico</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">Tellico</name>
  <name xml:lang="et">Tellico</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Tellico</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Tellico</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">Tellico</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Tellico</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Tellico</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxTellicoxx</name>
  <summary>Collection Manager</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Gestor de col·leccions</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">Collection Manager</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="et">Kogude haldur</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Collectiebeheer</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Gestor de Colecções</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Gerenciador de Coleções</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Samlingshanterare</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Програма для керування збірками</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxCollection Managerxx</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      Tellico is an application for organizing your collections.
      It provides default templates for books, bibliographies, videos, music, video games, coins, stamps, trading cards, comic books, and wines.
      It allows you to enter your collection in a catalogue database, saving many different properties like title, author, etc.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El Tellico és una aplicació per organitzar col·leccions. Proporciona plantilles per defecte per llibres, bibliografies, vídeos, música, videojocs, monedes, segells, cromos, còmics i vins. Permet introduir les col·leccions en una base de dades de catàlegs, desant moltes propietats diferents com el títol, l'autor, etc.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Tellico is an application for organising your collections. It provides default templates for books, bibliographies, videos, music, video games, coins, stamps, trading cards, comic books, and wines. It allows you to enter your collection in a catalogue database, saving many different properties like title, author, etc.</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">Tellico on kõikvõimalike kogude haldamiseks mõeldud rakendus. See pakub vaikimisi malle raamatute, bibliograafiate, videode, muusika, videomängude, müntide, markide, mängukaartide, koomiksite ja veinide tarbeks. Rakenduses saab oma kogu sisestada kataloogi andmebaasi, kuhu salvestatakse hulk omadusi, näiteks nimi, autor jne.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Tellico is een toepassing voor het organiseren van uw verzamelingen. Het biedt standaard sjablonen voor boeken, bibliografieën, video's, muziek, videogames, munten, postzegels, visitekaartjes, strips en wijnen. Het stelt u in staat om uw verzameling in een catalogusdatabase in te voeren, waarin veel verschillende eigenschappen, zoals titel, auteur, etc. opgeslagen kunnen worden.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O Tellico é uma aplicação para organizar as suas colecções. Oferece modelos predefinidos para livros, bibliografias, vídeos, músicas, jogos de vídeo, moedas, selos, cromos, livros de banda desenhada, vinhos, entre outras colecções. Permite-lhe introduzir a sua colecção numa base de dados de catálogos, gravando diversas propriedades, como o título, o autor, etc.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Tellico é um aplicativo para organizar suas coleções. Oferece modelos predefinidos para livros, bibliografias, vídeos, músicas, jogos de vídeo game, moedas, selos, figurinhas, histórias em quadrinhos, vinhos, entre outras coleções. Permite-lhe introduzir sua coleção em um banco de dados de catálogos, gravando diversas propriedades, como título, autor, etc.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Tellico är ett program för att organisera samlingar. Det tillhandahåller standardmallar för böcker, bibliografier, videor, musik, videospel, mynt, frimärken, samlarbilder, serier och viner. Det låter dig mata in samlingen i en katalogdatabas, och spara många olika egenskaper som titel, författare, etc.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Tellico — програма для упорядковування ваших збірок. У ній передбачено типові шаблони для збірок книг, бібліографій, відео, музичних творів, відеоігор, нумізматики, марок, карток, коміксів та вин. За її допомогою ви зможете вести записи у форматі бази даних, зберігаючи різноманітні дані щодо елементів збірки, зокрема дані щодо назви, автора тощо.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxTellico is an application for organizing your collections. It provides default templates for books, bibliographies, videos, music, video games, coins, stamps, trading cards, comic books, and wines. It allows you to enter your collection in a catalogue database, saving many different properties like title, author, etc.xx</p>
    <p>Features:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Característiques:</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Features:</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">Omadused:</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Mogelijkheden:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Características:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Funcionalidades:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Funktioner:</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Можливості:</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxFeatures:xx</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Supports default collections of books, bibliographic entries, videos, music, video games, comic books, coins, stamps, trading cards, wines, board games, and file catalogs</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Funciona amb col·leccions per defecte de catàlegs de llibres, entrades bibliografies, vídeos, música, videojocs, còmics, monedes, segells, cromos, vins, jocs de taula i fitxers</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Supports default collections of books, bibliographic entries, videos, music, video games, comic books, coins, stamps, trading cards, wines, board games, and file catalogues</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Vaikimisi on toetatud, raamatute, bibliograafiliste kirjete, videode, muusika, videomängude, koomiksite, müntide, markide, mängukaartide, veinide, lauamängude ja failikataloogide kogud</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Ondersteunt standaard verzamelingen van boeken, bibliografie-items, video's, muziek, videogames, strips, munten, postzegels, visitekaartjes, wijnen, bordspellen en catalogs van bestanden</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Suporta diversas colecções de livros, itens bibliográficos, vídeos, músicas, jogos de vídeo, livros de banda desenhada, moedas, selos, cromos, vinhos, jogos de tabuleiros e catálogos de ficheiros</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Suporte a diversas coleções de livros, itens bibliográficos, vídeos, músicas, jogos de vídeo game, histórias em quadrinhos, moedas, selos, figurinhas, vinhos, jogos de tabuleiro e catálogos de arquivos</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Stöder standardsamlingar för böcker, bibliografiposter, videor, musik, videospel, serier, mynt, frimärken, samlarbilder, viner, brädspel och filkataloger</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Підтримка типових збірок книг, бібліографічних записів, відео, музики, відеоігор, коміксів, нумізматики, марок, карток, вин, настільних ігор та каталогів файлів.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxSupports default collections of books, bibliographic entries, videos, music, video games, comic books, coins, stamps, trading cards, wines, board games, and file catalogsxx</li>
      <li>Supports user-defined custom collections</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Funciona amb col·leccions personalitzades definides per l'usuari</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Supports user-defined custom collections</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Toetatud on ka kasutaja loodud kohandatud kogud</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Ondersteunt gebruikergedefinieerde eigen verzamelingen</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Suporta colecções personalizadas pelo utilizador</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Suporte a coleções personalizadas pelo usuário</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Stöder användardefinierade anpassade samlingar</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Підтримка визначених користувачем нетипових збірок.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxSupports user-defined custom collectionsxx</li>
      <li>Supports any number of user-defined fields, of several different types: text, paragraph, list, checkbox, number, URL, date, images, and combinations</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Funciona amb qualsevol nombre de camps definits per l'usuari, de molts tipus diferents: text, paràgraf, llista, caselles de selecció, nombre, URL, data, imatges, i combinacions</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Supports any number of user-defined fields, of several different types: text, paragraph, list, tickbox, number, URL, date, image, and combinations</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Toetatud on mis tahes hulk kasutaja määratud välju, mis võivad olla väga eri tüüpi: tekst, lõik, loend, märkekast, arv, URL, kuupäev, pilt või nende kombinatsioon</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Ondersteunt elk aantal gebruikergedefinieerde velden met verscheidene verschillende types: tekst, paragraaf, lijst, keuzevakje, aantal, URL, datum, afbeelding en combinaties</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Suporta qualquer número de campos definidos pelo utilizador, de diferentes tipos: texto, parágrafo, lista, opção de marcação, número, URL, data, imagens e combinações</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Suporte a qualquer número de campos definidos pelo usuário, de diferentes tipos: texto, parágrafo, lista, opção de marcação, número, URL, data, imagens e combinações</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Stöder hur många användardefinierade fält som helst av flera olika typer: text, stycke, lista, kryssruta, tal, webbadress, datum, bilder och kombinationer</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Підтримка довільної кількості визначених користувачем полів записів: текст, абзац, список, поле для позначки, номер, адреса, дата, зображення та будь-які інші комбінації.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxSupports any number of user-defined fields, of several different types: text, paragraph, list, checkbox, number, URL, date, images, and combinationsxx</li>
      <li>Handles entries with multiple authors, genres, keywords, etc</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Gestiona entrades amb diversos autors, gèneres, paraules clau, etc</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Handles entries with multiple authors, genres, keywords, etc</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Raskusi ei valmista ka kirjed, mis sisaldavad mitut autorit, žanri, võtmesõna jne.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Behandelt items met meerdere auteurs, genres, zoektermen, etc.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Lida com itens de vários autores, géneros, palavras-chave, etc</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Lida com itens de vários autores, gêneros, palavras-chave, etc</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Hanterar poster med flera författare, genrer, nyckelord, etc.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Обробка записів з декількома авторами, жанрами, ключовими словами тощо.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxHandles entries with multiple authors, genres, keywords, etcxx</li>
      <li>Automatically formats titles and names</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Formata automàticament els títols i els noms</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Automatically formats titles and names</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Pealkirjasid ja nimesid saab lasta automaatselt vormindada</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Deelt automatisch titels en namen in</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Formata automaticamente os títulos e nomes</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Formata automaticamente os títulos e nomes</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Formaterar automatiskt titlar och namn</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Автоматичне форматування заголовків та назв.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxAutomatically formats titles and namesxx</li>
      <li>Supports collection searching and view filtering</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Admet la cerca de col·leccions i filtratge de vista</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Supports collection searching and view filtering</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Toetatud on kogudes otsimine ja vaate filtreerimine</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Ondersteunt zoeken in verzamelingen en filtering op weergave</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Suporta a pesquisa na colecção e a filtragem da janela</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Suporte a pesquisa na coleção e filtragem da janela</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Stöder sökning i samlingen och filtrering av visningen</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Підтримка пошуку у збірці та фільтрування даних для перегляду.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxSupports collection searching and view filteringxx</li>
      <li>Sorts and groups collection by various properties</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Ordena i agrupa les col·leccions per diverses propietats</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Sorts and groups collection by various properties</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Kogusid saab sortida ja rühmitada eri omaduste järgi</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Sorteert en groepeert verzameling door verschillende eigenschappen</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Ordena e agrupa a colecção de acordo com diversas propriedades</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Ordena e agrupa a coleção de acordo com diversas propriedades</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Sorterar och grupperar samlingen enligt olika egenskaper</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Упорядковування та групування збірки за різноманітними властивостями.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxSorts and groups collection by various propertiesxx</li>
      <li>Allows customizable entry templates through XSLT</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Admet plantilles d'entrades personalitzades mitjançant XSLT</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Allows customisable entry templates through XSLT</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">XSLT abil on võimalik luua kohandatud kirjemalle</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Staat aanpasbare sjablonen van items toe via XSLT</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Permite modelos de registos personalizados, através de XSLT</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Permite modelos de registros personalizados, através de XSLT</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Tillåter anpassningsbara inmatningsmallar via XSLT</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Придатні до налаштовування шаблони записів на основі XSLT.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxAllows customizable entry templates through XSLTxx</li>
      <li>Imports MODS, Bibtex, RIS, CSV, PDF metadata, and many other formats</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Importa MODS, Bibtex, RIS, CSV, metadades de PDF, i molts altres formats</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Imports MODS, Bibtex, RIS, CSV, PDF metadata, and many other formats</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">MODS-i, Bibtexi, RIS-i, CSV, PDF-i metaandmete ja veel paljude vormingute import</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Importeert MODS, Bibtex, RIS, CSV, PDF metadata en vele andere formaten</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Importa dos formatos MODS, Bibtex, RIS, CSV, meta-dados de PDF, entre muitos outros</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Importa dos formatos MODS, Bibtex, RIS, CSV, metadados de PDF, entre muitos outros</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Importerar MODS, Bibtexd, RIS, CSV, PDF-metadata och många andra format</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Імпортування метаданих MODS, Bibtex, RIS, CSV, PDF та даних у багатьох інших форматах.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxImports MODS, Bibtex, RIS, CSV, PDF metadata, and many other formatsxx</li>
      <li>Exports to Bibtex, ONIX, CSV, HTML, PilotDB, and other formats</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Exporta a Bibtex, ONIX, CSV, HTML, PilotDB, i altres formats</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Exports to Bibtex, ONIX, CSV, HTML, PilotDB, and other formats</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Eksport Bibtexi, ONIX-i, CSV, HTML-i, PilotDB ja veel paljudesse vormingutesse</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Exporteert naar Bibtex, ONIX, CSV, HTML, PilotDB en andere formaten</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Exporta para o Bibtex, ONIX, CSV, HTML, PilotDB, entre outros formatos</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Exporta para o Bibtex, ONIX, CSV, HTML, PilotDB, entre outros formatos</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Exporterar till Bibtex, ONIX, CSV, HTML, PilotDB och andra format</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Експортування даних у форматах Bibtex, ONIX, CSV, HTML, PilotDB тощо.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxExports to Bibtex, ONIX, CSV, HTML, PilotDB, and other formatsxx</li>
      <li>Imports information directly from Amazon.com, IMDb, z39.50 servers, PubMed, SRU servers, CrossRef.org, various other websites, and from external scripts</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Importa informació directament des d'Amazon.com, IMDb, servidors z39.50, PubMed, servidors SRU, CrossRef.org, altres llocs web, i des d'scripts externs</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Imports information directly from Amazon.com, IMDb, z39.50 servers, PubMed, SRU servers, CrossRef.org, various other websites, and from external scripts</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Teabe importimine otse Amazon.com-ist, IMDb-st, z39.50 serveritest, PubMed-ist, SRU serveritest, CrossRef.org-ist, veel paljudelt veebilehekülgedelt ja väliste skriptide kaudu</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Importeert informatie direct uit Amazon.com, IMDb, z39.50-servers, PubMed, SRU-servers, CrossRef.org, verschillende andere websites en uit externe scripts</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Importa a informação directamente a partir da Amazon.com, IMDb, servidores de z39.50, PubMed, servidores de SRU, CrossRef.org, entre outros serviços, bem como de programas externos</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Importa a informação diretamente a partir da Amazon.com, IMDb, servidores z39.50, PubMed, servidores SRU, CrossRef.org, entre outros serviços, bem como de scripts externos</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Importerar information direkt från Amazon.com, IMDb, z39.50-servrar, PubMed, naSRU-servrar, CrossRef.org, diverse andra webbplatser, och från externa skript</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Імпортування даних безпосередньо із серверів Amazon.com, IMDb, z39.50, PubMed, SRU, CrossRef.org, інших сайтів та на основі зовнішніх скриптів.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxImports information directly from Amazon.com, IMDb, z39.50 servers, PubMed, SRU servers, CrossRef.org, various other websites, and from external scriptsxx</li>
      <li>Imports CDDB data for cataloging audio CDs</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Importa dades CDDB per la catalogació de CD d'àudio</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Imports CDDB data for cataloguing audio CDs</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">CDDB andmete import audio-CD-de kataloogimiseks</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Importeert CDDB-gegevens voor catalogiseren van audio-cd's</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Importa os dados do CDDB para catalogar os CD's de áudio</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Importa os dados CDDB para catalogar CDs de áudio</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Importerar CDDB-data för katalogisering av ljud-cd</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Імпортування даних CDDB для каталогізації звукових компакт-дисків.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxImports CDDB data for cataloging audio CDsxx</li>
      <li>Scans and imports audio file collections, such as mp3 or ogg</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Explora i importa col·leccions de fitxers d'àudio, com MP3 o OGG</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Scans and imports audio file collections, such as mp3 or ogg</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Helifailide (näiteks mp3 või ogg) kogude läbiuurimine ja import</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Scant en importeert verzamelingen van audio-bestanden, zoals mp3 of ogg</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Sonda e importa as colecções dos ficheiros de áudio, como MP3's ou OGG's</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Verifica e importa as coleções de arquivos de áudio, como MP3 ou OGG</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Söker igenom och importera samlingar av ljudfiler, såsom mp3 eller ogg</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Сканування та імпортування збірок звукових файлів, зокрема mp3 та ogg.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxScans and imports audio file collections, such as mp3 or oggxx</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">http://tellico-project.org/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=tellico</url>
  <url type="faq">http://tellico-project.org/faq</url>
  <url type="help">http://docs.kde.org/development/en/extragear-office/tellico/index.html</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default" width="867" height="627">
      <image>http://kde.org/images/screenshots/tellico.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>tellico</binary>
  </provides>
</component>
